Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Churchill, Winston, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Clark, Emily, 1939 (Box 12)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1934-1964 (Box 12)
  - Clyne, William Patrick, 1933-1941 (Box 12)
  - Coates, Robert M., undated (Box 12)
  - Cocktail party, 1933-1934 (Box 12)
  - [Abe] Cohen's Exchange Inc., 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - College Art Association, 1932-1938 (Box 12)
  - Collins Publishers, See Knittel, Robert/Rainer, Luise.
  - Color photography, 1934; undated (Box 12)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System Inc., 1935-1964; undated (Box 12)
    See also Wershba, Joe.
  - Columbia Lecture Bureau, 1941-1942 (Box 12)
  - Columbia Pictures Corporation, 1933-1934; undated (Box 12)
  - Columbia University, 1933-1970 (Box 12)
  - Commercial Solvents Corporation, 1936-1937 (Box 12)
  - Concert Management Arthur Judson, Inc., 1934 (Box 12)
  - Conde Nast Publications, Inc., 1929-1941; undated (Box 12)
  - Congoleum-Nairn Corporation, 1936-1937; undated (Box 12)
  - Cook, Marion Belden, 1935-1937 (Box 12)
  - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1949 (Box 12)
  - Corbett, Edith, 1934 (Box 12)
  - Cord, Walter (Stars & Stripes), 1952; includes photographs of MBW taken by Harry Koorajian, Signal Corps photographer (Box 12)
  - Cornell University, 1932-1939; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Cornell University, 1940-1971; undated (Box 13)
  - Cosmopolitan, 1933-1936 (Box 13)
  - Cousins, Norman and Ellen, 1939-1971; undated (Box 13)
  - Coxe, Daniel and Dorothy, 1936-1969; undated (Box 13)
  - Crane, Arnold H., 1966 (Box 13)
  - Cromie, Robert, 1933-1963 (Box 13)
  - Crone, Berta, 1934 (Box 13)
  - Crowninshield, Frank, undated (Box 13)
  - Culinary, 1950s (Box 13)
  - Cunningham, Imogen, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Curtis, E. P. "Ted", 1932-1966 (Box 13)
  - Cushman, Helen Caldwell, 1951-1963; undated (Box 13)
  - D, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Daily Times (Chicago), 1933 (Box 14)
  - Dam assignments, 1934-1936; undated (Box 14)
  - Darien Community Association, 1956-1967 (Box 14)
  - Dearing, Albin Pasteur, 1939 (Box 14)
  - Andre Debrie, 1931-1934 (Box 14)
  - De Liagre, Alfred and Mrs., 1931-1939 (Box 14)
  - Delineator Editorial Offices, 1934-1936; undated (Box 14)
  - Delman Inc., 1934-1935 (Box 14)
  - Deskey, Donald, 1932-1934 (Box 14)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1933-1966 (Box 14)
  - Deutsche Botschaft, undated (Box 14)
  - DeVries, Lini, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Dewey, John and Evelyn, 1932-1939 (Box 14)
  - [M. H.] de Young Memorial Museum, 1932-1933 (Box 14)
  - Diehl, Ambrose and Frances, 1933-1967; undated (Box 14)
  - Directions, See Harris, Marguerite Tjader.
  - Dodd, Martha, 1938-1939 (Box 14)
  - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1935; 1940 (Box 14)
  - Dombo,"Tubby" Luf, 1931-1966; undated (Box 14)
  - [R. R.] Donnelly & Sons Company, 1942; 1970 (Box 14)
  - Dorne, Albert, 1964; 1967 (Box 14)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1938 (Box 14)
    See also Meyer, Rose D.
  - Dreyfuss, Henry, 1934-1942 (Box 14)
  - Drought assignment, Aug. 1934-1935; undated (Box 14)
  - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 14)
  - Dugan, Tom, 1953; undated (Box 14)
  - The Dupont Magazine, 1934-1935; undated (Box 14)
  - Durant, Kenneth C. and Clara, 1933-1963; undated (Box 14)
  - Duryea, Drix, 1933-1935; undated (Box 14)
    See also National Broadcasting Company (NBC).
  - Dust storm assignments, 1935; 1954,; undated (Box 15)
  - E, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Earhart, Amelia, 1933-1934 (Box 15)
    See also Putnam, George Palmer.
  - Earle, Harley, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Eastern Airlines job, 1935-1963; undated; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - [George] Eastman House exhibitions, 1956-1965 (Box 15)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1930-1956; undated; 3 folders (Box 15)
    See also Newhall, Beaumont and Nancy.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 1943 (Box 15)
  - Eisenstaedt, Alfred and Kathy, 1947-1971; undated (Box 15)
    See also Time, Inc.
  - Elliott Company, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Elson, Robert, See Time, Inc.
  - Employees, 1934-1935 (Box 15)
  - Erwin, Wasey & Company, Inc., 1933-1939; undated (Box 15)
  - Esquire, 1933-1957; undated (Box 16)
  - European trips, 1938-1939 (Box 16)
  - Evander Childs High School exhibit, 1964 (Box 16)
    See also United States Information Service.
  - Exhibition catalogs (miscellaneous), 1931-1968; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Experimental Cinema, See Stern, Seymour.
  - "Eyes on Russia" and "Red Republic" (motion pictures), 1932-1934; undated (Box 16)
  - F-Fk, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Fl-Fz, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Fairchild Aerial Camera Corporation, 1935-1937 (Box 17)
  - Fairfield County Trust Company, 1957-1966 (Box 17)
  - Famous Photographers School, 1964-1968; undated (Box 17)
  - Farrar, Straus and Cudahy, Inc., 1955-1957; undated (Box 17)
  - Federation for the Support of Jewish Philanthropic Societies of New York City, 1934-1959 (Box 17)
  - Feibleman, James Kern, undated (Box 17)
  - Fern, Alan, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Film and Photo League, 1933-1935; undated (Box 17)
  - Film Society Inc., 1933-1937; undated (Box 17)
  - Finlay Colour Limited, 1933-1934 (Box 17)
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Company, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Fischer, Louis and Markoosha, 1932-1964 (Box 17)
  - Fisher, Ray and Sue, 1960-1971 (Box 17)
  - Fitelson, H. William, 1932-1936; undated (Box 17)
  - Fleming, Archibald Lang, 1937-1952 (Box 17)
  - Fletcher & Ellis, Inc., 1934-1935 (Box 17)
  - Fleury, Serge, 1933-1934 (Box 17)
  - Flintkote Company, 1934-1936 (Box 17)
  - Foley, Martha, 1934; 1938 (Box 17)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1934-1935 (Box 17)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1933-1942 (Box 18)
  - Form letters, 1932-1936 (Box 18)
  - Forsee, Aylesa, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
  - Fortiner, Virginia J., 1934; undated (Box 18)
  - Fortune, See Time, Inc.
  - Frary, Ihna Thayer, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Fratkin, Ethel (employee), 1932-1960; undated; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Freeman, Joseph, 1931-1963 (Box 18)
  - Fred F. French Management Company, 1933-1938 (Box 18)
  - Friends of the Soviet Union, 1932-1938; undated (Box 18)
  - Fritzsche Brothers, Inc., 1935-1936 (Box 18)
  - Fuller, Richard Buckminster, 1933 (Box 18)
  - Fuller & Smith & Ross, Inc., 1933-1939 (Box 18)
  - G-Grd, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Gre-Gz, 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Gafney, Hugh, 1934-1967; undated (Box 19)
  - Gale Company, 1930-1944; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Gallagher, Barrett, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Galleon Press, Inc., 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Gannett, Lewis Stiles and Ruth Crisman, 1934-1936 (Box 19)
  - Gardening, 1939 (Box 19)
  - Gardner Advertising Company, 1929-1939 (Box 19)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, 1929-1944; undated (Box 19)
  - Geer, Will and Herta, 1939; undated (Box 19)
  - General Biological Supply House, 1937-1938 (Box 19)
  - General Electric Company, 1930-1935 (Box 19)
  - General Motors Corporation, 1934-1935; undated (Box 19)
  - General Printing Corporation, 1935 (Box 19)
  - George Eastman House exhibitions, See Eastman House exhibitions.
  - Georgian (USSR) songs, 1934 (Box 19)
  - Gernsheim, Helmut, 1957; 1970 (Box 19)
  - Getchell, J. Stirling, 1934-1936 (Box 19)
  - Gibson, Lydia, 1934 (Box 19)
  - Gilbert, Ariadne, 1944-1963 (Box 19)
  - Giles, Barbara, See New Masses.
  - Gilfillan, Francois Archibald, 1925-1963 (Box 20)
  - Ginn and Company: Publishers, 1936-1941 (Box 20)
  - Glintenkamp, H., 1938-1939 (Box 20)
    See also American Artists Congress.
  - Goldwyn, Samuel, 1934; 1943 (Box 20)
  - Good Housekeeping, 1934-1958 (Box 20)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1933-1937; undated (Box 20)
  - Gorham Company, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Grace & Holiday, 1930-1935 (Box 20)
  - Graebner, Walter, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Graflex, 1930-1957; undated (Box 20)
  - Graubner, Oscar A., 1933-1963; undated (Box 20)
  - Grauert, Charlotte (Klien), 1930-1965 (Box 20)
  - Great Lakes Exposition, 1936 (Box 20)
  - Green, Kenneth, See Lehmann-Haupt, Hellman and Letitia.
  - Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst, 1951-1971 (Box 20)
  - Greenwald, Dorothy, undated (Box 20)
  - Greer, Howard, 1937-1939 (Box 20)
  - Griffin, Arthur and Claire, 1962; undated (Box 20)
  - Griffin, Florence, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Griffith, Sanford, 1933-1938 (Box 20)
  - Grimm, Peter, 1951-1970; undated (Box 20)
  - Grolier Incorporated, 1941-1964 (Box 20)
  - Gruppo, Nelson, 1933 (Box 20)
  - [John Simon] Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1939 (Box 20)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1933-1936 (Box 20)
  - Gulf Refining Company, See Gulf Oil Corporation.
  - Gumpertz, Julian, 1934-1937 (Box 21)
  - Gunther, John, 1931-1959 (Box 21)
  - H, 6 folders (Box 21)
  - H.E.R. Laboratories, Inc., 1932-1936 (Box 21)
  - Habicht, Hermann R., 1931 (Box 21)
  - Halle Brothers, 1934-1966; undated (Box 22)
  - Haloid Company, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Hamilton, William, 1933 (Box 22)
  - [C. S.] Hammond & Company, 1935-1936 (Box 22)
  - Hanc, Joseph, 1938 (Box 22)
  - Hanff-Metzger, Inc., 1933-1936; undated (Box 22)
  - Hanson, Joseph E., 1968 (Box 22)
  - Harcourt, Brace & Company, 1937-1959 (Box 22)
  - Harno, Albert James, 1944 (Box 22)
  - Harper & Brothers, 1934-1935 (Box 22)
  - Harris, Marguerite Tjader, 1957; undated (Box 22)
  - Harvard University, 1930-1968 (Box 22)
  - Hawes, Elizabeth, 1933-1938; undated (Box 22)
  - Hearst Enterprises, Inc., 1933-1938 (Box 22)
  - Heilman, Robert D., 1963 (Box 22)
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1938-1941 (Box 22)
    See also North America Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy in N (general).
  - Henny, Keith, 1935 (Box 22)
  - Henry Street Visiting Nurse Service, 1936-1938; undated (Box 22)
  - Hepburn family, 1936 (Box 22)
  - Heppenstall Steel Company, 1933-1934 (Box 22)
  - Herrick, Frances, 1939; undated (Box 22)
  - Hession, Eileen, 1957-1961 (Box 22)
  - Heyman, Ken, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Heyman, Mark, 1933 (Box 22)
  - Hicks, Wilson, See Time, Inc.
  - Hiett, Helen, 1958-1964; undated (Box 22)
  - Higgins, Lisetta, 1957-1964 (Box 22)
  - Hill, John W., 1930-1963 (Box 22)
  - Himber, Charlotte, 1942 (Box 22)
  - Hindus, Maurice Gerschon, 1930-1963 (Box 22)
  - Hinni, K. T., 1961-1968; undated (Box 22)
  - Hitler, Adolf, 1940 (Box 22)
  - Hood, Robert E., 1962-1968 (Box 22)
  - Hoover, Dorothy, See Time, Inc.
  - House & Garden, See Conde Nast Publications, Inc.
  - Household, 1957-1970; undated (Box 22)
  - Howe, James Wong, 1935 (Box 22)
  - Hudson's Bay Company, 1937-1938 (Box 22)
    See also Bonnycastle, Richard H. G.
  - Hughes, Wolff & Company, 1933-1935 (Box 22)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1965 (Box 22)
  - Hussey, Margaret Parton, See Parton, Margaret.
  - Hutchins, C. T., 1931-1935 (Box 22)
  - I, 1 folder (Box 23)
  - The Illustrated London News, 1930-1936 (Box 23)
  - Inches, Howard Von Hardenburg, 1935-1937 (Box 23)
  - Indianapolis Motor Speedway Corporation, 1935; includes MBW's pit pass (Box 23)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph and Marian, 1933-1959; undated (Box 23)
    See Time, Inc.
  - International Correspondence Schools, 1934-1936 (Box 23)
  - International Exhibition of Photography, 1933 (Box 23)
  - International Harvester Company, 1935; 1960 (Box 23)
  - International Labor Defense, 1933-1938; undated (Box 23)
  - International Paper Company, 1937-1944 (Box 23)
  - Ives, Burl, 1950 (Box 23)
  - J, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Phyllis, 1964-1971; undated (Box 23)
  - Jaffe, Herb, 1956-1964 (Box 23)
  - Jakobovits, Leon A., 1965 (Box 23)
  - James, Frederick, 1946 (Box 23)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1961 (Box 23)
  - Jayasinghe, Peter L., 1946-1963; undated (Box 23)
  - Jenkins, Florence Foster, 1938 (Box 24)
  - Jenter Exhibits, Inc., 1934-1937 (Box 24)
  - Jesuits, 1953-1968; undated; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Jewell, Edward Alden, 1933-1935 (Box 24)
  - Jinnah, Fatima, 1946 (Box 24)
  - "Journeyman" (play), 1937-1938 (Box 24)
  - K, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Albert Kahn, Inc., 1934-1936 (Box 24)
  - Karas, George, See Time, Inc.
  - Karsh, Yousef, 1963-1966 (Box 24)
  - Katz, Nathan, 1937-1938 (Box 24)
  - Kearney, Josephine (employee), 1929-1932 (Box 24)
  - Keasbey, Edie and Tom, 1964-1967; undated (Box 24)
  - Keelor & Stites Company, 1933 (Box 24)
  - Keen, Kennard G., 1935; undated (Box 24)
  - Keep, O. D., 1935-1937; undated (Box 24)
  - Keller, Helen, 1938 (Box 24)
  - Kelley, Etna, 1934-1938 (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Fred C., 1933; undated (Box 24)
    See also Commercial Solvents Corporation.
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1936-1939 (Box 24)
  - Kenyon & Eckhardt, 1933-1934 (Box 24)
  - Keppler, Victor, 1933-1937; undated (Box 24)
    See also Famous Photographers School.
  - Kerner, Robert Joseph, 1938-1939 (Box 25)
  - Ketchum, Carl J., 1933 (Box 25)
  - Ketchum, Macleod & Grove, Inc., 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Khama, Seretse and Ruth, 1950-1953; undated (Box 25)
  - King Features Syndicate, Inc., 1934-1964 (Box 25)
  - Kingsbury, John Adams, 1932-1937 (Box 25)
  - Kirchwey, Freda, 1937-1939 (Box 25)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1935 (Box 25)
  - Kitts, Alfred, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Klarnet, Philip, 1956-1969; undated (Box 25)
  - Knittel, Robert/Rainer, Luise, 1963-1965 (Box 25)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche Wolf, 1935-1960 (Box 25)
  - Kopf, Elizabeth (employee), 1934-1937 (Box 25)
  - Kopperl, Bert (employee), 1938-1963 (Box 25)
  - Korner, Ruth, 1938-1939 (Box 25)
  - Kostelanetz, Andre, 1944 (Box 25)
  - Arthur Kudner Inc., 1935-1936; undated (Box 25)
  - Kuh, Frederick, 1930-1964; undated (Box 25)
    See also United Press.
  - Kupcinet, Irv, 1960 (Box 25)
  - L-Lk, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Ll-Lz, 1 folders (Box 26)
  - Laboratory School of Industrial Design, 1939 (Box 26)
  - Ladies' Home Journal, 1933-1960; undated (Box 26)
  - La Montaine, John, 1964-1968; undated (Box 26)
    See also Memorabilia: Miscellany: Music/John La Montaine.
  - Lange, Dorothea, 1939-1966 (Box 26)
  - Langner, Lawrence, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
  - League of American Writers, 1937-1939 (Box 26)
  - League of Women Shoppers, 1935-1939; undated (Box 26)
  - Lehigh Portland Cement Company, 1940-1941; undated (Box 26)
  - Lehmann-Haupt, Hellman and Letitia, 1933-1934; undated (Box 26)
  - Leigh, Colston, 1933-1968; undated (Box 26)
  - Leighton, Clare, 1933-1935 (Box 26)
  - Leitch, Norma "Paddy" Dershimer, 1933-1935; undated (Box 26)
  - Lengyel, Emil, 1935-1936 (Box 26)
  - Lennen & Mitchell, Inc., 1933-1935 (Box 26)
  - Leroux, Germaine/Safranek, Milos, 1939; undated (Box 26)
  - Letchworth Village, 1933-1938 (Box 26)
  - Levarie, Siegmond, 1959; 1964,; undated (Box 26)
  - Lieber, Maxim, 1936-1942; undated (Box 26)
    See also "Journeyman" (play).
  - Life, See Time, Inc.
  - Lindsay, John V., 1961; undated (Box 26)
  - Liss, Joseph, 1959-1964; undated (Box 26)
    See also Memorabilia: Miscellany: Writings by others.
  - Litvinov, Maxim, 1933-1942 (Box 26)
  - Lloyd-Smith, Parker, See Time, Inc.
  - Lloyds Film Storage Corporation, 1934-1938 (Box 26)
  - Loewy, Raymond, 1936 (Box 26)
  - London Electrotype Agency, 1931-1935; undated (Box 26)
  - Longwell, Daniel, See Time, Inc.
  - Loomis, Louise Ropes, 1933 (Box 26)
  - Lord & Taylor, 1932-1939 (Box 26)
  - Lord & Thomas Advertising, 1933-1936 (Box 26)
  - Louisville flood assignment, 1937 (Box 26)
  - Love, N. Stewart, 1936-1939; undated (Box 27)
  - Lower, Elmer, See Time, Inc.
  - Lubin, Isadore, 1934-1936 (Box 27)
  - Luce, Henry R., Clare Boothe and family, 1935-1963; undated (Box 27)
  - Ludewig & Deutsch, 1932-1936; undated (Box 27)
  - Ludlum Steel Company, 1929-1937 (Box 27)
    See also Wm. B. Remington, Inc.
  - Lugene, Inc., 1933-1936 (Box 27)
  - Lynn, Rhoda (employee), 1940-1942 (Box 27)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1931-1934 (Box 27)
  - M-Mim, 5 folders (Box 27)
  - Min-Mz, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - McBride, Mary Margaret, 1933-1942; undated (Box 28)
  - McCall Company/McCall's, 1933-1968; undated (Box 28)
  - McCann-Erickson Inc., 1932-1937; undated (Box 28)
  - McGarry, William A., 1931-1937; undated (Box 28)
  - [J. S.] McHugh, Inc., 1934-1940 (Box 28)
  - Mackland, Ray, See Time, Inc.
  - MacMannus, John & Adams, Inc., 1932-1937 (Box 28)
  - Macmillan Company, 1931-1935; undated (Box 28)
  - McNiff, Alice E., 1966-1968 (Box 28)
  - [R. H.] Macy & Co., 1932-1963; undated (Box 28)
  - Magnuson, Libby (employee), 1957-1963; undated (Box 28)
  - Magonet, Fern, See Time, Inc.
  - Maloney, Thomas J., 1933-1966; undated (Box 29)
  - Mandell, Maurice, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Marin, John, 1933 (Box 29)
  - Marine Midland Trust Co., 1946-1957 (Box 29)
  - [A. N.] Marquis Company, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Marshall, Bratter & Seligson, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Marshall College, See Leigh, Colston.
  - Marshall Field & Company, 1931-1942 (Box 29)
  - Martin, Jackie, 1936-1968 (Box 29)
  - Martin, Miles Jay, 1936-1938 (Box 29)
  - Mayer, Arthur L., 1934; 1958 (Box 29)
  - Mayer, Carlos, 1932-1934; undated (Box 29)
  - Medical Bureau to Aid Spanish Democracy, 1934-1939 (Box 29)
  - Medo Photo Supply Corporation, 1935-1940 (Box 29)
  - Meiss, Edwin R., 1934-1960; undated (Box 29)
  - Meldrum and Fewsmith, Inc., 1930-1936; undated; 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Mellon Institute of Industrial Research, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Menchin, Robert S., 1965 (Box 30)
  - Meng, Chih, 1939 (Box 30)
  - Meredith Publishing Company, 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Metcalf, Jim, 1945 (Box 30)
  - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, 1932-1938; undated (Box 30)
  - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes, 1932-1935 (Box 30)
  - Meyer, Rose D., 1932 (Box 30)
  - Mezhlauk, V. I., 1931-1937 (Box 30)
  - Michelson, Herman, See New Masses.
  - Miki, Jun and Yasuko, 1958-1966 (Box 30)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1933 (Box 30)
  - Milgrim, 1933-1936 (Box 30)
  - [George W.] Millar & Co., 1932-1940 (Box 30)
  - Millard, Charles W., 1966 (Box 30)
  - I. Miller & Sons, Inc., 1931-1935 (Box 30)
  - Mills, Robert and Ann P., 1963 (Box 30)
  - Mills College, 1933-1935 (Box 30)
  - Monnet, Jean, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Montgomery Ward & Co., 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Moore, Iola Willie, 1937-1939 (Box 30)
  - Moraes, Frank, 1945-1968; undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Morang, Alfred, 1937 (Box 30)
  - Morgan, Willard D., 1942-1963 (Box 30)
  - [C. V.] Mosby Company, 1933-1939 (Box 30)
  - Muller-Munk, Peter, 1932-1944 (Box 31)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1933-1937; undated (Box 31)
  - Mumm-Romer-Robbins & Pearson, 1934-1936 (Box 31)
  - Munger, Jessie "Mother", 1931-1955; undated (Box 31)
  - Munkacsi, Martin, 1935 (Box 31)
  - Murphy, Francis X., 1941 (Box 31)
  - Murray, D. C."Bill", See Adcraft Club of Detroit; Time, Inc.
  - Arthur Murray's Studio, 1935-1960; undated (Box 31)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1963-1964 (Box 31)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1931-1966; undated (Box 31)
  - Muslim, Faesol, 1962 (Box 31)
  - N, 3 folders (Box 31)
  - Nair, Pyarelal, 1968 (Box 32)
  - Nakano, Goro, 1955 (Box 32)
  - "Naked Eye" (motion picture), 1958-1960 (Box 32)
  - Nakian, Reuben, 1934-1936; undated (Box 32)
  - Nathan, Adele Gutman, undated (Box 32)
  - The Nation, 1932-1936 (Box 32)
  - National Alliance of Art and Industry Inc., 1932-1935 (Box 32)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 1933-1960; undated; 2 folders (Box 32)
  - National Engraving Company, 1931-1932; undated (Box 32)
  - National Foundation for Infant Paralysis, 1952-1958 (Box 32)
  - National Geographic Society, 1934-1936 (Box 32)
  - National League of American Pen Women, Inc., 1957-1968; undated (Box 32)
  - National Recovery Administration (NRA), See United States. National Recovery Administration.
  - National Studios Inc., 1932-1935 (Box 32)
  - National Urban League, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 32)
  - NEA Service, Inc., 1932-1938; undated (Box 32)
  - Neher, Irene, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal, undated (Box 32)
  - New Canaan Library exhibit, 1963-1964; undated (Box 33)
  - New Jersey State Museum, 1936 (Box 33)
  - New Masses, 1933-1942; undated (Box 33)
  - The New Republic, 1934-1938; undated (Box 33)
  - New School for Social Research, 1933-1939; undated (Box 33)
  - New Workers School, 1934; undated (Box 33)
  - New York (State). Department of Commerce, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1932-1934 (Box 33)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1932-1959 (Box 33)
  - New York Institute of Photography, 1934-1936 (Box 33)
  - New York Post, See Wershba, Joe.
  - New York Telephone Company, 1931-1939 (Box 33)
  - The New York Times, 1930-1963; undated (Box 33)
    See also Wiley, Louis.
  - New York University, 1937-1963 (Box 33)
  - Newell Emmett Company, 1932-1936; undated (Box 33)
  - Newhall, Beaumont and Nancy, 1936-1971; undated (Box 33)
    See also Museum of Modern Art.
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, 1936-1937; undated (Box 33)
  - Nichols, Elaine, 1945 (Box 33)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1969 (Box 33)
  - North, Joseph, See New Masses.
  - Nye, Gertrude, 1931-1939 (Box 33)
  - O, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Oglesby, Catherine, 1934-1947 (Box 33)
    See also Ladies' Home Journal.
  - Ohio State University, 1932-1969; undated (Box 33)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1932-1936; undated (Box 34)
  - Open Road, Inc., 1931-1935 (Box 34)
  - Openhym, Evelyn Tennyson, 1932-1937 (Box 34)
  - Otis Steel Company, 1931-1953 (Box 34)
  - Oumansky, K., 1933-1939; undated (Box 34)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, 1939-1971 (Box 34)
  - Owen, Ray and Gladys, 1963 (Box 34)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass Company, 1931-1932; undated (Box 34)
  - Oxford Paper Company, 1932-1942 (Box 34)
  - P-Pp, 4 folders (Box 34)
  - Pr-Pz (Box 35)
  - Pacific Western Airlines, 1957 (Box 35)
  - Pan American Airways, 1934-1942; undated; includes souvenir Air Mail envelope with ornate gold stamp of Pan Am logo and "Territory of Hawaii" surrounding tiny black-and-white photo of man with water buffalo (Box 35)
  - Papurt, M. Jerry, 1943-1944; undated; 4 folders (Box 35)
  - Pardoe, J. B., 1931-1939; undated (Box 35)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1938 (Box 35)
    See also American Friends Service Committee.
  - Parkinson's Disease
    - Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960; 12 folders (Box 36)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1971; undated; 12 folders (Box 37)
    - Medical misc. (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
    - Printed material (Box 38)
  - Parshalle, Eve, 1963 (Box 38)
  - Parton, Margaret, 1963 (Box 38)
  - Pearce, Charles A., See Harcourt, Brace & Company.
  - Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, 1939 (Box 38)
  - Peel, Fred P., 1933-1935 (Box 38)
  - Pegler Case, 1947-1952; undated; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Pellissier, Raoul, 1933-1934 (Box 39)
  - Pennsylvania Museum of Art, 1932-1934 (Box 39)
  - Pepin, Lee, 1957-1958 (Box 39)
  - Perkins Institute and Massachusetts School for the Blind, 1932-1963 (Box 39)
  - Perry, Helen Swick, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Philadelphia East-West Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 39)
    See also Pegler Case.
  - Phillips, John, 1959-1969; undated (Box 39)
  - Phillips Academy, 1934-1941 (Box 39)
  - Photo League, 1938-1941 (Box 39)
  - Photographic Illustrators, Inc., 1933-1936; undated (Box 39)
    See also United States. National RecoveryAdministration (NRA).
  - Photographic Society of America, 1935-1962; undated (Box 39)
  - Photographic Society of Philadelphia, 1932 (Box 40)
  - Photographic Workers League, 1933 (Box 40)
  - Photokina, 1958-1969 (Box 40)
  - Pictorial Photographers of America, 1930-1938; undated (Box 40)
  - Pictorial Review, 1931-1936 (Box 40)
  - Pierce-Arrow Motor Car Company, 1931-1935; undated (Box 40)
  - Pilnyak, Boris, 1931-1935 (Box 40)
  - Pittsburgh assignment, 1937; undated (Box 40)
  - Plainfield High School, 1934-1971 (Box 40)
  - Platinel, Inc., 1931-1932 (Box 40)
  - PM, 1940-1941; undated (Box 40)
  - Podolsky, M., 1932 (Box 40)
  - Pollack, Peter, 1957-1963 (Box 40)
  - Pollak, Bernard E., 1931-1932 (Box 40)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham, 1933-1939 (Box 40)
  - Popular Photography, 1937-1967 (Box 40)
  - Postal Telegraph-Cable Company, 1931-1937 (Box 40)
  - Powers Reproduction Corporation, 1935-1941 (Box 40)
  - Preston, Scherer, 1931-1932 (Box 40)
  - Price Brothers Sales Corporation, 1932-1936; See also Publicity. (Box 40)
  - Printers' Ink Monthly, 1933-1964 (Box 40)
  - Professional Photographers Club of New York, Inc., 1931-1933 (Box 40)
  - Professional Photographers of America, 1933-1966 (Box 40)
  - Prudden, Bonnie, 1964-1966; undated (Box 40)